# 大家好 上次我看到兄弟家那個地裡面啊
Hi everyone! Last time I saw a lot of wild passion fruits,
# 好多那個野生的百香果啊
in my buddy's field.
# 我去看一下
Let me go and have a look.
# 就在前面一點點
It's just right in front of us.
# 這條路都被兄弟封起來了啦
The path has already been blocked by my buddy.
# 你看 這就是百香果哦
Look! These are the passion fruits.
# 好多哇
A lot!
# 好小的
They're very small.
# 大是挺 有些也很大哦
The big ones are, some are rather big in fact.
# 有些長那麼大啦
Some are already that big now.
# 没熟 里面不紅
They're still green, not red inside.
# 你看 好多哇
Look! Here are a lot.
# 沒 沒熟哇
They're, they're not yet ripe.
# 那麼多天怎麼還不熟
Why are they still not ripe after so many days?
# 哎呀 有一個
Aya! Here's one.
# 有個有點點黃的
This one is a tiny little bit yellow,
# 有一點點黃哦
a little bit yellow,
# 一點點紅哦
a little bit red.
# 這一個
This one.
# 你看 這個
Look! This one,
# 有一點點紅啊
is a little bit red.
# 哎喲
Hayo!
# 這肉
The pulp
# 嗯
Um hm!
# 酸的
It's sour,
# 好酸啊
very sour!
# 哎喲 好像有一點甜甜哦
Ayo? It's seems to be a little bit sweet.
# 真的很好吃嘞
It's really tasty.
# 比外面買的要好吃
It's so much better than those bought outside.
# 你看 這個果肉
Look at the pulp!
# 晶瑩剔透的哦
Isn't it crystal clear?
# 看吃那個食物 (註︰字幕應該有點錯，他似乎是說甚麼看著食欲就來之類的？)
It looks so,
# 食欲來啦
so appetizing.
# 嗯
Um hm!
# 可以
Not bad
# 哎呀 好酸
Aya! It's so sour.
# 下次來 下次熟了之後我們再來摘
Next time! We'll come again next time when they are more ripened.
# 好多都沒熟的
Many are still not yet ripe.